(Raj:)Sure, I sit on the floor
for years, no one cares.
(Raj:)The pretty white girl's
there ten seconds,
(Raj:)and suddenly we're
all running to IKEA.
(Sheldon:)No one is running anywhere.
(Sheldon:)We're not getting
a dining room table.
(Leonard:)I know you don't like change,
but it's not a terrible idea.
(Penny:)You guys never use
that space up there.
(Penny:)Why not get a table?
(Sheldon:)Do you want the long answer
or the short answer?
(Howard:)How come we never get that option?
(Sheldon:)Chaos theory suggests that
even in a deterministic system,
(Sheldon:)if the equations describing
its behavior are nonlinear,
(Sheldon:)a tiny change
in the initial conditions
(Sheldon:)can lead to a cataclysmic
and unpredictable result.
(Penny:)Translation?
Wah! I don't want a table!